#### Resume

I am Gabriel de Rezende Gonçalves, a 21-year-old software engineer who graduated from Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Campinas and took a technical course in Computer Science at ETEC Bento Quirino. I work as a full-stack developer, with advanced knowledge in languages, frameworks, and technologies such as JavaScript, React, Node.js, Vue.js, NoSQL, MySQL, PHP, and Laravel. In addition, I have experience in Flutter for mobile application development.

## Contact

**Email:** contato@gabireze.com.br **LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/gabireze

Site: gabireze.com.br

GitHub: github.com/gabireze

Professional Experience

# Assistant Software Developer at Encora Inc.

January 2023 - Present

Write code according to project specifications; Perform software testing to ensure quality and integrity of code; Debug code issues and fix them; Keep technical documentation up-to-date; Monitor project progress and report to project managers; Collaborate with software developers as a team to ensure efficient and effective project completion.

# **Software Development Intern** at **Encora Inc.**

February 2021 - January 2023

Learn about programming languages and tools used in software development; Assist software developers in writing code, testing, and debugging; Attend technical meetings and presentations; Keep technical documentation up-to-date; Monitor project progress and report to project managers.

## **Software Development Intern** at OpaBox

June 2019 - February 2021

Actively work on coding projects and contribute to creating apps and systems. Check and fix software issues to ensure the final product's quality, collaborate with the development team to ensure that projects comply with standards and good development practices, familiarize yourself with new technologies, and develop your programming skills while working on real projects. Attend meetings and communicate with other company departments, including project management, design, and sales.

## **Software Development Intern** at <a href="SuperOpa">SuperOpa</a>

June 2019 - February 2021

Actively participates in development projects by writing code and contributing to the construction of apps and systems, is responsible for testing and debugging software to ensure the final product's quality, collaborates with the development team to ensure that projects comply with standards and good development practices, has the opportunity to learn new technologies and develop programming skills while working on real projects, and attends meetings with other company departments.

#### Qualifications

#### Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Campinas

Bachelor's degree, Software Engineering (2019 - 2022)

#### Escola Técnica Estadual "Bento Quirino"

Technical High School, Computing · (January 2016 - December 2018)

Language skills

Inglês - Upper Intermediate Espanhol - Technical / Basic Português - Fluent / Native

## Additional information

**Academic Exchanges** at the Canadian College of English Language - CCEL July 2022 · Vancouver, Canada

B2 English level - English 125 (Upper Intermediate); 38 lessons per week; Basics Classes + 2 Electives.

#### Technical skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Dart, C, Java, PHP, Laravel.
- React, Flutter, Vue.js, AngularJS, Bootstrap.
- Node.js, Express.js, Serverless Framework.
- MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL.
- npm, Git, Swagger, Docker, Jira, Trello, Figma, Postman, Slack, SCRUM, Kanban, Mailtrap, Form.io, Zeplin.
- Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Linux, macOS, Windows, Linux.
- Firebase, AWS, Amazon DynamoDB, Lambda, S3, CloudFront, API Gateway, CloudWatch, SQS.

# Interpersonal Skills

- Creativity, Persuasion, Collaboration, Adaptability, Time Management
- Organization of groups, Negotiation of solutions, Empathy, Social Sensitivity
- Emotional self-awareness, Emotional control, Self-motivation
- Recognition of emotions in other people, Skill in interpersonal relationships